<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artifacts and Reflections on Digital Revolutions and Convergence Culture</title>
    <link>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artifacts and Reflections on Digital Revolutions and Convergence Culture</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 12:08:50 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Selection 3 Reflection</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/post/selection-3-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:04:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/post/selection-3-reflection/</guid>
      <description>What? What is the artifact within the larger context of the course/experience?
This is a collaborative share, done with Brendan, Lianna, and Kamilla, that represents our readings of assemblage theory. It came during the first part of our readings on assemblage. It also came during the week of Jody Shipka&amp;rsquo;s visit and workshop for the rhetoric and composition program. To say that assemblage was on my mind would be an understatement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selection 3: Collaborative Assemblage</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/post/selection-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:04:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/post/selection-3/</guid>
      <description>For this third selection, I chose a collaborative blog post on assemblage. The post can be found here, and I&amp;rsquo;ve copied the text of the post below, though the color of the fonts did not carry with it.
A reflection on this piece can be found here
Isn&amp;rsquo;t Assemblage All of the Things?: An assemblage by Kamila, Michael, Liana, and Brendan We could think of assemblage as a way of composing using “disparate elements” or the “use, reuse, and repurposing of materials” (Yancey and McElroy 4).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selection 2 Reflection</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/post/selection-2-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 12:30:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/post/selection-2-reflection/</guid>
      <description>What? What is the artifact within the larger context of the course/experience?
This artifact was the second major composing assignment that we had this semester. It also came due right after traveling to Feminisms and Rhetorics, so this context colored my experiences. The conversation between Jessi and I which lead to this topic was a good experience of using AirBnB for a trip to St. Augustine. This intersected with various discussions and uses of Uber and other sharing-economy apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selection 2: AirBnB Circulation Map</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/post/selection-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 12:30:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/post/selection-2/</guid>
      <description>I did a thought experiment for the circulation of a hypothetical room share through airbnb. In doing so, I didn’t trace how a specific composition has circulated, but the ways in which the sharing economy of airbnb works through a variety of circulated information, actions, materials, and locations. I was also interested in how it has changed, and draws from, prior mediated forms of sharing and rental economies, imagining what it might look-like without the centralized authority and app to organize and coordinate the sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selection 1 Reflection</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/post/selection-1-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 18:45:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/post/selection-1-reflection/</guid>
      <description>What? This selection is the SRR that I wrote on The Social Life of Information. It was originally due during Hurricane Irma, and it was a weird one in the ways in which it fit in this strange start to the semester. It was also a piece written when, while we were technically three weeks into the semester, we hadn’t met much yet.
So what? I chose this SRR for a few reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selection 1: SRR The Social Life of Information</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/post/selection-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 18:35:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/post/selection-1/</guid>
      <description>Selection 1: Thinking about Networks, Interfaces, and Open-Source In The Social Life of Information, Seely Brown and Duguid explore the expansion of information and information technologies, and the effects on the people, products, business, education, and lives of these involved. They largely focus on important business and industrial players, and the ways in which they had evolved during the late 1990s. They also look at the shifting economic and cultural forces, examining how formalized structures are slow to adapt to the changing realities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>