<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reflection on Digital Revolutions and Convergence Culture</title>
    <link>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/tags/reflection/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reflection on Digital Revolutions and Convergence Culture</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 23:50:20 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/tags/reflection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Technology and Literacy: Two Perspectives on a System</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/reflection/technology-and-literacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 23:50:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/reflection/technology-and-literacy/</guid>
      <description>I would like to start back at the beginning
Notecard Front    The front of the notecard with definitions from the first day of class. The questions that guided each entery are: What does it mean to be literate? and Why and/or how is this important?   Notecard Back    These represent changing in my earlier definitions as prompted during different points in the semester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyword: Circulation</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/reflection/circulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 23:14:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/reflection/circulation/</guid>
      <description>If you post to instagram, but no-one sees it, does it count? What about if no-one likes it? How does it change? This is a series of questions that I have been repeating, a lot and with slight variations, over the last few weeks of teaching. The idea of circulation gets to much of how I understand and continue to work with texts, especially digital ones. This has much to do with how texts do work in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyword: Memory</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/reflection/memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 23:14:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/reflection/memory/</guid>
      <description>Memory is an idea that I feel emerged from my readings and work this semester. I didn&amp;rsquo;t see it having an explicit exploration in the readings, but I do see it as an important component with how people interact with technology, what they hope it does, and their literacy experiences. I see traces of memory in Porter, with his discussions of technology and how it changed/changes, and in the ideas of (re)Mediation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keywords: Bodies and Space</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/reflection/bodies-and-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 23:14:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/reflection/bodies-and-space/</guid>
      <description>This section represents less of an overt discussion on the literature and through the class, but has informed my thinking. It is difficult for me to see technology and literacy as separated from people in time and space interacting with thing. This has much to do with Standage&amp;rsquo;s theories of circulation, but it comes down to, for me, moments of interaction between people and their stuff, with the intention of having that stuff do something with/by/through/to other people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyword: Assemblage</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/reflection/assemblage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 23:13:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/reflection/assemblage/</guid>
      <description>Assemblage is a concept that I latched onto this semester. I found it useful in illuminating a variety of composing processes and situations. It also made a useful bridge between the material and cognitive realities of composing and literacy practices. It has been something that I have worked to continue to inhabit and embody throughout this reflection and ePortfolio. It has been a concept that has been useful to &amp;ldquo;retheorize writing, especially given the current interest in materiality and technology&amp;rdquo; (Yancey and McElroy 17).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Semester Reflection</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 23:11:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/digital-revolutions-eportfolio/reflection/</guid>
      <description>Thinking Through, With, and Alongside: Bodies, Texts, and Technologies In thinking through this semester in Digital Revolutions/Convergence Culture, I see technology and literacy engaged in systems of meaning through which people navigate space, time, and material. Technology and literacy offer ways of making meaning through these juxtapositions and shifts in perspective. I have seen myself thinking about how literacy shapes and is shaped by technology, and how actors/subjectivities/bodies align themselves with, alongside, and through the technologies that are used.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>